{
    "subject": "resource/Artem_Yarchuk",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Yaroslavl",
    "human_readable": "Artem Yarchuk died in Yaroslavl.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9443153142929077,
            "question": "Was Artem Yarchuk from Yaroslavl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.827854335308075,
            "question": "Where did Artem Yarchuk die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5808937549591064,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about the circumstances of Artem Yarchuk's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5639306902885437,
            "question": "What is significant about Yaroslavl in relation to Artem Yarchuk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37880751490592957,
            "question": "Are there any other details available about Artem Yarchuk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37435010075569153,
            "question": "What is known about Artem Yarchuk's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3099066913127899,
            "question": "Were there any notable events or connections associated with Artem Yarchuk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30679866671562195,
            "question": "What impact did Artem Yarchuk's life have on others?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2991366982460022,
            "question": "Who might have known Artem Yarchuk personally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1876457780599594,
            "question": "Is there a way to learn more about Artem Yarchuk's legacy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Artem Yarchuk died in Yaroslavl.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5691_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might have known Artem Yarchuk personally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5691_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Artem Yarchuk's life have on others?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5691_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable events or connections associated with Artem Yarchuk?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5691_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5691_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5691_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5691_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5691_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5691_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5691_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5691_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5691_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5691_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5691_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Artem Nikolayevich Yarchuk (also referred to as Artem Yarchuk) was among those who perished in the plane crash near Yaroslavl, Russia on September 7, 2011. Therefore, the statement \"Artem Yarchuk died in Yaroslavl\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n    }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}